http://scifispace.com/privacy-policy/

Search
Search for:
Search
Search for:
Search
Who we are
We are an independent science fiction community and news website (located at https://www.Scifispace.com) not associated with any network, studio or streaming service (no, we are not part of SyFy Channel).
What personal data we collect and why we collect it
Comments & Forum Posts
When visitors leave comments or posts/replies on the forums on the site we collect the data shown in the comments form, and also the visitor’s IP address and browser user agent string to help spam detection.
An anonymized string created from your email address (also called a hash) may be provided to the Gravatar service to see if you are using it. The Gravatar service privacy policy is available here: https://automattic.com/privacy/. After approval of your comment, your profile picture is visible to the public in the context of your comment.
You may opt-in to also publish your comment on Facebook. Facebook comments are subject to Facebook’s privacy policy published at https://www.facebook.com/privacy/explanation
Media
If you upload images to the website, you should avoid uploading images with embedded location data (EXIF GPS) included. Visitors to the website can download and extract any location data from images on the website. Please be certain to give attribution to any photos or video you upload including the original source.
Contact forms
Information collected via contact forms is for our internal use only for the purpose stated on the form. We do not sell or rent any information such as name or email address.
Cookies
If you leave a comment on our site you may opt-in to saving your name, email address and website in cookies. These are for your convenience so that you do not have to fill in your details again when you leave another comment. These cookies will last for one year.
If you have an account and you log in to this site, we will set a temporary cookie to determine if your browser accepts cookies. This cookie contains no personal data and is discarded when you close your browser.
When you log in, we will also set up several cookies to save your login information and your screen display choices. Login cookies last for two days, and screen options cookies last for a year. If you select “Remember Me”, your login will persist for two weeks. If you log out of your account, the login cookies will be removed.
If you edit or publish an article, an additional cookie will be saved in your browser. This cookie includes no personal data and simply indicates the post ID of the article you just edited. It expires after 1 day.
Embedded content from other websites
Articles on this site may include embedded content (e.g. videos, images, articles, etc.). Embedded content from other websites behaves in the exact same way as if the visitor has visited the other website.
These websites may collect data about you, use cookies, embed additional third-party tracking, and monitor your interaction with that embedded content, including tracking your interaction with the embedded content if you have an account and are logged in to that website.
Analytics
Who we share your data with
All analytical data collected is for internal use only. We do not collect or store specific information such as your name or email address. We may share visitor counts including by country or city location for the purpose of selling advertising to support our site, but no specific user information is shared.
How long we retain your data
If you leave a comment, the comment and its metadata are retained indefinitely. This is so we can recognize and approve any follow-up comments automatically instead of holding them in a moderation queue.
For users that register on our website (if any), we also store the personal information they provide in their user profile. All users can see, edit, or delete their personal information at any time (except they cannot change their username). Website administrators can also see and edit that information. It is never shared, sold or rented with any 3rd party.
What rights you have over your data
If you have an account on this site, or have left comments, you can request to receive an exported file of the personal data we hold about you, including any data you have provided to us. You can also request that we erase any personal data we hold about you. This does not include any data we are obliged to keep for administrative, legal, or security purposes.
Where we send your data
Visitor comments may be checked through an automated spam detection service. If you choose to share a comment on Facebook, it is subject to their Privacy Information published here https://www.facebook.com/privacy/explanation
No other data is sold, rented or sent to any 3rd party.
Your contact information
Any contact information you share with use including your name, email or physical address, phone number, ip address etc, is for our internal use only to contact you, allow you to contribute articles and media to the site, ship prizes or material for review, etc. We never sell, rent or share this information with anyone for any reason.
Additional information
How we protect your data
Our site uses SSL encryption on a secured, private server with no access other than our technical support staff, administrative staff, or web hosts. We do no collect or store any financial or other data.
Comment with Facebook
Get the best stories straight into your inbox!
Email address:
Leave this field empty if you're human: Don't worry, we don't spamad astra
aquaman
archives
avengers
batman
ben affleck
brad pitt
buffy
captain marvel
wonder woman
ScifiLori on Loki and Scarlet Witch series on the horizon?
facebook
twitter
instagram
youtube
Don’t miss out on new posts
Email address:
Leave this field empty if you're human: Don't worry, we don't spam
Scifispace.com has been providing science-fiction fans news, reviews, and fun since 1998. Our latest version offers a more social community with member forums, groups which includes collaboration to write fan-fic and your own stories, and so much more. Join us on our voyage of discovery of all things nerd, geek, and scifi. This site is for news & information only. All images are copyrighted to their respective owners. All content cited is derived from their respective sources. Scifispace.com is not associated with SyFy Channel or any other station or network.
How to Write for Us
How to Submit an Event
How to Advertise with Us
About Scifispace.com
Contact Scifispace.com
Privacy Policy
RSS Feed
SiteMap
Something went wrong. Check YouTube API key and channel ID.
@ScifiSpace
Subscribe
Announcements
Books & Authors
Games
Movie Reviews
Other News
Scifi Movie News
Scifi Series
Avengers: Endgame is a Satisfying Wrap-UpLoki and Scarlet Witch series on the horizon?Constantine Reboot in Development with Matt RyanJames Gunn Rehired to Direct Guardians 3Ghostbusters 3 Continues the LegacyScifiLori on Loki and Scarlet Witch series on the horizon?
© 2020 by Scifispace.com. All rights reserved.
Search for:
Forgot password?
Don't have an account? Register
Forgot password?
Enter your account data and we will send you a link to reset your password.
Username or Email Address
Back to Login
Your password reset link appears to be invalid or expired.
Log in
Privacy Policy
To use social login you have to agree with the storage and handling of your data by this website. %privacy_policy%
Here you'll find all collections you've created before.
